<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RC Controller</string>
    <string name="title_activity_camera">CameraActivity</string>
    <string name="host">Host</string>
    <string name="port">Port</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="empty_string"> </string>
    <string name="distance_text">Distance: </string>
    <string name="distance_measure">cm</string>
    <string name="speed_text">Speed: </string>
    <string name="speed_measure">km/h</string>
    <string name="dark_mode">Dark Theme</string>
    <string name="r_string">R</string>
    <string name="line_label_desc">Line label</string>
    <string name="distance_keeping">Keep Distance</string>
    <string name="keep_contained">Keep Contained</string>
    <string name="change_direction">Change Turning Direction</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit Application</string>
    <string name="poweroff">Turn Off System</string>
    <string name="hot_road">Hot Road</string>
    <string name="ACCESS_WIFI_STATE"> ❗ The WIFI state permission is needed to detect the RC car on your network, so the app can autoconnect to it.\n</string>
    <string name="BLUETOOTH"> ❗ The BLUETOOTH permission is needed, so the app can handle the bluetooth of your phone (turn it on/off).\n</string>
    <string name="ACCESS_FINE_LOCATION"> ❗ The LOCATION permission is needed for both the WIFI, and the BLUETOOTH functionality of the app, hence it is needed in order to continue.\n</string>
    <string name="ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE"> ❗ The NETWORK state permission is needed to detect the RC car on your network, so the app can autoconnect to it.\n</string>
    <string name="BLUETOOTH_ADMIN"> ❗ The BLUETOOTH ADMIN permission is needed in order to scan the area for nearby devices, like the RC car, so the app can autoconnect to it.\n</string>
    <string name="INTERNET"> ❗ The INTERNET permission is needed to detect the RC car on your network, so the app can autoconnect to it.\n</string>
    <string name="ACCESS_BACKGROUND_LOCATION"> ❗ The BACKGROUND LOCATION permission is needed, in order for the app to use bluetooth features, so the app can handle the bluetooth of your phone (turn it on/off).\n</string>
    <string name="TURN_WIFI_ON"> ❗ Please turn on your wifi before you continue in order to autodetect devices on your network. If you have a RC car connected to the same network that your phone, the app will connect to it automatically.\n</string>
    <string name="TURN_BLUETOOTH_ON"> ❗ Please enable the app to turn on your bluetooth in order to autodetect devices near you. If you have a RC car near you, the app will connect to it automatically.\n</string>
</resources>
